Linval Muchapirei

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

Energetic and curiosity-driven Software Engineer with 3+ years of experience writing top quality clean code. Specializing in Software Planning, Design and development. Competent in web technologies both front-end and back-end using tools and technologies such as Golang, NodeJS and Java based frameworks. Experience with Restful API design and development, Microservices and gPRC. Passionate about programming in general especially Golang and its simplicity and capabilities.Looking for a challenge and learn from the best developers.

PERSONAL DETAILS

7888 Belevedere West Harare

Zimbabwe

CONTACT

- linvle2@gmail.com
- +263787452541

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer At Community Dental Partners

COMMUNITY DENTAL PARTNERS

April 2021-Present

Full stack development using web technologies to deliver web based internal tools used in dental healthcare Duties-Design and development of UI on frontend and business logic on the backend using ReactJS with both JavaScript and typescript on frontend ,backend development using NodeJS Typically receive a story detailing what must be done and then you work on the apps and apply changes appropriately either on frontend or backend

Software Development Intern

PRODLEADER ENTERPRISES

June 2019-June 2020

Design and implementation of software solutions for fiscal(TAX) devices required by clients to comply with TAX Regulations. Developed internal app to track jobs and services done to clients Duties-Developed a desktop based application to interface with fiscal device and then sign invoices generated by the client

EDUCATION

BTech Software Engineering

HARARE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Learning Foreign Languages

Aug 2017-Aug 2021

SKILLS

Software Engineering Analytical Skills Open-mindedness Unit Testing Collaboration Object-Oriented Design Functional Programming **INTERESTS LANGUAGES** Cooking Shona Football Coaching English Reading German Programming Languages and Compiler Theory